Guide to the Portland Reporter Photographs Collection 1960-1964
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Subject Files, circa 1900-1965; 1960-1965; Series A
  - Sketches, 1962 (Box-folder 35/41)
  - Skid Row, 1961 (Box-folder 35/42)
  - Skidmore Fountain, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Skiing, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Skin, 1964 (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Skin diving, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Skyline Memorial Garden Chapel, 1962 (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Skyline Mortuary, 1962 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Slingshots, 1962 (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Slot machines, 1961; 1963; 1964 (Box-folder 36/8)
  - Smith Lake, 1963 (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Smoke jumpers, 1964 (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Snake River, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Snakes, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Snow, 1961-1962; 1968 (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Snow Bunny Lodge, 1962 (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/15)
  - Soccer, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/16)
  - Social Security, 1962 (Box-folder 36/17)
  - Softball, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/18)
  - Somerset West, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 36/19)
  - Space, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/20)
  - Space--Astronauts--Oregon, 1964 (Box-folder 36/21)
  - Space capsule, 1961 (Box-folder 36/22)
  - Space laboratory, 1964 (Box-folder 36/23)
  - Space--Man shot, 1964 (Box-folder 36/24)
  - Spacemen, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 36/25)
  - Space--Planetoid, 1961 (Box-folder 36/26)
  - Space station, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36/27)
  - Space suit, 1961 (Box-folder 36/28)
  - Space vehicles, 1964 (Box-folder 36/29)
  - Spain, 1963 (Box-folder 36/30)
  - Speelyai Bay--Lewis River, Wash., 1961 (Box-folder 36/31)
  - Spinning wheel, 1963 (Box-folder 36/32)
  - Spirit Lake, Wash., 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 36/33)
  - Spring, 1963 (Box-folder 36/34)
  - Squash, 1961 (Box-folder 36/35)
  - Stadium, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 36/36)
  - Stamps, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 36/37)
  - State Laundry and Dry Cleaning, 1961 (Box-folder 36/38)
  - Statues, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 36/39)
  - Statues--Lincoln, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 36/40)
  - Statues--Statue of Liberty, 1961 (Box-folder 36/41)
  - Steam baths, 1962 (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Steel cleaning, 1963 (Box-folder 128/27)
  - Still, 1964 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Stock Exchange, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Storms, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Storms--Portland, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Stoves, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Strawberries, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 37/7)
  - Streets
    - Barbur, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Burnside, 1961 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Canyon Road, 1960 (Box-folder 37/10)
    - Columbia Boulevard, 1961 (Box-folder 37/11)
    - Front, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 37/12)
    - Harbor Drive, 1962 (Box-folder 37/13)
    - Jefferson, 1961 (Box-folder 37/14)
    - Laura S.E., 1964 (Box-folder 37/15)
    - Macadam, 1964 (Box-folder 37/16)
    - Mill, 1962 (Box-folder 37/17)
    - Minnesota, 1961 (Box-folder 37/18)
    - Minnesota, 1961 (Box-folder Oversize B/4)
    - Portland, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 37/19)
    - Sandy, 1963 (Box-folder 37/20)
    - Slavin Road, 1960 (Box-folder 37/21)
    - Sylvan, 1960 (Box-folder 37/22)
  - Street crossing, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 37/23)
  - Street curbs, 1961 (Box-folder 37/24)
  - Street lights, 1961 (Box-folder 37/25)
  - Street signs, 1964 (Box-folder 37/26)
  - Streetcars, 1963 (Box-folder 37/27)
  - Streetcars--New York, 1962 (Box-folder 37/28)
  - Streetcars--Portland, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 37/29)
  - Streetcars--San Francisco, 1962 (Box-folder 37/30)
  - String, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 37/31)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1964 (Box-folder 37/32)
  - Students--Foreign, 1963 (Box-folder 37/33)
  - Studio--Seattle, 1964 (Box-folder 37/34)
  - Sugar beets, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 37/35)
  - Sugar--White satin, 1960 (Box-folder 37/36)
  - Suicide, 1962 (Box-folder 37/37)
  - Sukka, 1964 (Box-folder 37/38)
  - Summer, 1961 (Box-folder 37/39)
  - Sun eclipse, undated (Box-folder 37/40)
  - Sun Valley, 1962 (Box-folder 37/41)
  - Sunshine Division, 1961 (Box-folder 37/42)
  - Supermarkets, 1961 (Box-folder 37/43)
  - Supreme Court, 1962 (Box-folder 38/1)
  - Swan Island, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 38/2)
  - Sweeney, Krist and Dimm, 1961 (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Swift and Co., 1961 (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Swimming, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Swimming pool--Columbia Park, 1960 (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Switzerland, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 38/7)
  - Sylvan Park, 1960 (Box-folder 38/8)
  - Symphony Ball, 1964 (Box-folder 38/9)
  - Symphony--Boston, 1963 (Box-folder 38/10)
  - Symphony--Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 38/11)
  - Symphony--Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 128/28)
  - Tacoma, Wash., 1961 (Box-folder 38/12)
  - Tahiti, 1961 (Box-folder 38/13)
  - Tanks, 1962 (Box-folder 38/14)
  - Teachers--Portland, 1961 (Box-folder 38/15)
  - Tahkenitch Lake, 1961 (Box-folder 38/16)
  - Teeth, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 38/17)
  - Tektronix, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 38/18)
  - Telephones, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 38/19)
  - Telephones--Bell System, 1960 (Box-folder 38/20)
  - Telephone cable, 1962 (Box-folder 38/21)
  - Telephones--Pacific Telephone Northwest, 1961 (Box-folder 38/22)
  - Telephone poles, 1961 (Box-folder 38/23)
  - Telequote, 1961 (Box-folder 38/24)
  - Telescopes, 1961 (Box-folder 38/25)
  - Television, 1962 (Box-folder 38/26)
  - Television, 1964 (Box-folder 128/29)
  - Television--KATU, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 38/27)
  - Television--KGW, 1961 (Box-folder 38/28)
  - Television--KOAP, 1962 (Box-folder 38/29)
  - Television towers, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 38/30)
  - Tennis, 1961 (Box-folder 38/31)
  - Tepee, 1964 (Box-folder 38/32)
  - Terminal I, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 38/33)
  - Terminal #4, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 38/34)
  - Terrorism--Venezuela, 1964 (Box-folder 38/35)
  - Terwilliger Plaza, 1961 (Box-folder 38/36)
  - Texas tower radar platform, 1964 (Box-folder 38/37)
  - Thailand, 1963 (Box-folder 38/38)
  - Thanksgiving, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 38/39)
  - Theater
    - Theaters, 1964 (Box-folder 38/40)
    - Ashland--Shakespeare Festival, 1964 (Box-folder 38/41)
    - Actors Ring, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 38/42)
    - G, 1964 (Box-folder 38/43)
    - H, 1961 (Box-folder 38/44)
    - Jewish Community Center, 1964 (Box-folder 38/45)
    - Lake Oswego Community Theater, 1963 (Box-folder 38/46)
    - The Muses, 1964 (Box-folder 38/47)
    - Paramount, 1961 (Box-folder 38/48)
    - Pentacle, 1964 (Box-folder 38/49)
    - Portland Civic, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Portland Civic, 1964 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Portland Junior Civic, 1961 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Portland Opera Assoc., 1964 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Rhododendron, 1964 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - S, 1961 (Box-folder 39/6)
  - Tidal wave [tsunami], 1964 (Box-folder 39/7)
  - Tidal wave, 1964 (Box-folder 128/30)
  - Tides, 1963 (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Tigard, Or., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Tillamook Head, 1964 (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Tillamook Burn, 1963 (Box-folder 128/31)
  - Timber, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Timber Structures, Inc., 1961 (Box-folder 39/12)
  - Timberline Lodge, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 39/13)
  - Timothy Lake, 1962 (Box-folder 39/14)
  - Tires, 1962 (Box-folder 39/15)
  - Titan missle base, 1961 (Box-folder 39/16)
  - Tivoli Gardens, 1964 (Box-folder 39/17)
  - Toledo, Or., 1961 (Box-folder 39/18)
  - Tomatoes, 1960 (Box-folder 39/19)
  - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, 1961 (Box-folder 39/20)
  - Tongue Point, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 39/21)
  - Tops--All Food Center, 1962 (Box-folder 39/22)
  - Torch of Learning, 1964 (Box-folder 39/23)
  - Tornedos, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 39/24)
  - Totem poles, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 39/25)
  - Totem pole marina, 1962 (Box-folder 39/26)
  - Tournament of Roses, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 39/27)
  - Towers--transmission, 1961 (Box-folder 39/28)
  - Toys, 1964 (Box-folder 39/29)
  - Toy and Joy Makers, 1962 (Box-folder 39/30)
  - Tracers, 1963 (Box-folder 39/31)
  - Track--Olympic team--U.S. team, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 39/32)
  - Track--Olympic trials, 1960 (Box-folder 39/33)
  - Track--Oregon State College, 1962 (Box-folder 39/34)
  - Track--Portland State College, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 39/35)
  - Tractors, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Tradewell Stores, 1963 (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Trading stamps, 1961 (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Traffic tickets, 1964 (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Trailers (includes mobile homes), 1960-1963 (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Trailers (includes mobile homes), 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Trains, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 40/7)
  - Train accident, 1964 (Box-folder 128/32)
  - Train accidents, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 40/8)
  - Train accidents, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 40/9)
  - Trains--model, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 40/10)
  - Trampoline, 1961 (Box-folder 40/11)
  - Tramways, 1963 (Box-folder 40/12)
  - Trees
    - Trees, general, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 40/13)
    - Albizzia, 1961 (Box-folder 40/14)
    - Cherry, 1961 (Box-folder 40/15)
    - Christmas, 1960 (Box-folder 40/16)
    - Clerodendron, 1961 (Box-folder 40/17)
    - Cottonwood, undated (Box-folder 40/18)
    - Davidia, 1961 (Box-folder 40/19)
    - Dogwood, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 40/20)
    - Douglas Fir, 1964 (Box-folder 40/21)
    - Fir, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 40/22)
    - Magnolia, 1961 (Box-folder 40/23)
    - Maple, 1961 (Box-folder 40/24)
    - Mugho Pine, 1961 (Box-folder 40/25)
    - Pine, 1961 (Box-folder 40/26)
    - Redwood, 1961 (Box-folder 40/27)
  - Tri-City (West Linn, Oregon City), 1963 (Box-folder 40/28)
  - Trolley, 1964 (Box-folder 40/29)
  - Truck accidents, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 40/30)
  - Trucks, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 40/31)
  - Trucks--Campers, 1962 (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Tualatin Country Club, 1964 (Box-folder 41/2)
  - Tualatin River, 1962 (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Tualatin River, 1964 (Box-folder 128/33)
  - Tuberculosis prevention, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Tugs, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Tugs--Starscrescent, 1961 (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Tumbling, 1962 (Box-folder 41/7)
  - Twins, 1962 (Box-folder 41/8)
  - Tygh Valley, 1962 (Box-folder 41/9)
  - Typewriters, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 41/10)
  - U and I Sugar, 1962 (Box-folder 41/11)
  - U-Save Membership Department Store, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41/12)
  - Umatilla County, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 41/13)
  - Umbrellas, 1960 (Box-folder 41/14)
  - Umpqua River, 1961 (Box-folder 41/15)
  - Underwood, Wash., 1961 (Box-folder 41/16)
  - Unicycle, 1964 (Box-folder 41/17)
  - Unidentified flying objects (UFO -- cross ref. only), 1964 (Box-folder 41/18)
  - Uniforms, 1964 (Box-folder 41/19)
  - Union Industrial Show, 1962 (Box-folder 41/20)
  - Union Station, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 41/21)
  - Unispere, 1961 (Box-folder 41/22)
  - United Good Neighbors, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 41/23)
  - United Medical Lab, 1962 (Box-folder 41/24)
  - United Nations, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41/25)
  - University of Chicago, 1961 (Box-folder 41/26)
  - University of Mississippi, 1962 (Box-folder 41/27)
  - University of Oregon
    - University of Oregon, general, 1964 (Box-folder 41/28)
    - Dental School, 1963 (Box-folder 41/29)
    - Haywood Field, 1963 (Box-folder 41/30)
    - Medical School, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 41/31)
    - Medical School Clinic, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41/32)
    - Medical School--Eye Clinic, 1961 (Box-folder 41/33)
    - Medical School--Primate Center, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41/34)
    - Museum of Art, 1961 (Box-folder 41/35)
    - Research Lab Building, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 41/36)
    - Vacation College, 1964 (Box-folder 41/37)
  - University of Portland, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 41/38)
  - University of Portland--Senior Citizens Home, 1961 (Box-folder 41/39)
  - University of Portland--Theater, 1962 (Box-folder 41/40)
  - University of Washington, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41/41)
  - Urban League, 1961 (Box-folder 41/42)
  - Urban renewal--South Auditorium, 1961 (Box-folder 41/43)
  - Utah--Arches Monument, 1961 (Box-folder 41/44)
  - Valley River Center, 1964 (Box-folder 42/1)
  - Vance Pit, 1963 (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Vancouver, Wash., 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Vancouver, Wash.--Fort Vancouver, 1960 (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Vancouver, Wash.--McGuire Chemical Co., 1960 (Box-folder 42/5)
  - Vancouver, Wash.--Port, 1960 (Box-folder 42/6)
  - Vandalism, 1964 (Box-folder 42/7)
  - Vehicles, 1961 (Box-folder 42/8)
  - Vending machines, 1962 (Box-folder 42/9)
  - Verboort, Or, 1961 (Box-folder 42/10)
  - Veteran's Day, 1961 (Box-folder 42/11)
  - Vienna Boys Choir, 1962 (Box-folder 42/12)
  - Vietnam, 1964 (Box-folder 42/13)
  - Vincennes, Ind., 1964 (Box-folder 42/14)
  - Violins, 1961 (Box-folder 42/15)
  - Visalia, Calif., 1964 (Box-folder 42/16)
  - Volcano, 1964 (Box-folder 42/17)
  - Voting, 1962 (Box-folder 42/18)
  - Wagons, 1963 (Box-folder 42/19)
  - Wagon wheels, 1961 (Box-folder 42/20)
  - Wagon wheels (Oregon Historical Society), 1964 (Box-folder 128/34)
  - Wallowa Lake, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 42/21)
  - Wallowa mountains, 1961 (Box-folder 42/22)
  - War Veterans Memorial, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 42/23)
  - War-- "Crush Malaysia" campaign, 1964 (Box-folder 42/24)
  - Warren Commission, 1964 (Box-folder 42/25)
  - Wasco County Courthouse, 1961 (Box-folder 42/26)
  - Washington, D.C.--Capitol Building, 1961 (Box-folder 42/27)
  - Washington, D.C.--Cultural Center, 1962 (Box-folder 42/28)
  - Washington, D.C.--White House, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 42/29)
  - Washington State Correction Center, 1964 (Box-folder 42/30)
  - Washougal River, 1961 (Box-folder 42/31)
  - Wastebasket, 1964 (Box-folder 42/32)
  - Water Laboratory (see also OSU Water laboratory), 1963 (Box-folder 42/33)
  - Water main, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 42/34)
  - Water pipes, 1962 (Box-folder 42/35)
  - Water skiiing, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 42/36)
  - Water tank, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 42/37)
  - Water tower, 1962 (Box-folder 128/35)
  - Watermelon (also cantelope), 1961 (Box-folder 42/38)
  - Water spout, 1961 (Box-folder 42/39)
  - Waverly Baby Home, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 42/40)
  - Weather forecast, 1964 Aug. 6 (Box-folder 42/41)
  - Weaving (Lummi Indians--see also knitting), 1963 (Box-folder 42/42)
  - Welding, 1961 (Box-folder 42/43)
  - Wells--Wonder Wells, 1960 (Box-folder 42/44)
  - West Berlin, 1964 (Box-folder 42/45)
  - West Linn, Or., 1963 (Box-folder 42/46)
  - West Point, 1961 (Box-folder 42/47)
  - Westen Business Builders, Inc., 1962 (Box-folder 42/48)
  - Western Farmers Assoc., 1960 (Box-folder 42/49)
  - Western Industrial Research Park, 1961 (Box-folder 42/50)
  - Western Light and Power Co., 1961 (Box-folder 42/51)
  - Western State Services, Inc., 1961 (Box-folder 42/52)
  - Western Union, 1960 (Box-folder 42/53)
  - Westport, Wash., undated (Box-folder 42/54)
  - Weyerhauser Paper Co., 1962 (Box-folder 42/55)
  - Wheat, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 43/1)
  - White Satin Sugar Co., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 43/2)
  - White Stag, 1962 (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Willamette National Forest, undated (Box-folder 43/4)
  - Willamette River, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Willamette University, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 43/6)
  - Willamette Valley Country Club, Canby, 1962 (Box-folder 43/7)
  - Wind, 1962 (Box-folder 43/8)
  - Wind mills, 1962 (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Wine cask, 1964 (Box-folder 43/10)
  - Witching stick, 1961 (Box-folder 43/11)
  - Wolff and Zimmer, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 43/12)
  - Wood, 1964 (Box-folder 43/13)
  - Woodburn Senior Estates, 1963 (Box-folder 43/14)
  - Wool, 1961 (Box-folder 43/15)
  - Woodland, Wash., 1962 (Box-folder 43/16)
  - Woolworth's, 1960 (Box-folder 43/17)
  - Workbench, 1963 (Box-folder 43/18)
  - World's Fair, 1961 (Box-folder 43/19)
  - Worms, 1961 (Box-folder 43/20)
  - Wrestling, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 43/21)
  - Wrestling--Portland State College, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 43/22)
  - X-ray, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 43/23)
  - Yacolt, Wash., 1961 (Box-folder 43/24)
  - Yamhill St., 1963 (Box-folder 43/25)
  - Yards, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 43/26)
  - YF 12 A Intercepter, 1964 (Box-folder 43/27)
  - Y.M.C.A., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43/28)
  - YMCA--Indian Guides, 1961 (Box-folder 43/29)
  - Youth Adventures Workshop, undated (Box-folder 43/30)
  - Youth Task Force, 1963 (Box-folder 43/31)
  - Yo-yos, 1963 (Box-folder 43/32)
  - YWCA, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 43/33)
  - Zarung Wood Preservative Company, 1961 (Box-folder 43/34)
  - Zell Brothers, 1960 (Box-folder 43/35)
  - Zellerback Paper Co., 1962 (Box-folder 43/36)
  - Zidell Exploration Inc.--Fire, 1961 (Box-folder 43/37)
  - Zoning, 1964 (Box-folder 43/38)
  - Zoo--Portland, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43/39)
  - Zoo--Portland, 1963 (Box-folder 128/36)
  - Zoo--Portland--Children's, 1963 (Box-folder 43/40)
  - Zoomsi, 1962 (Box-folder 43/41)
- People Files, 1960-1964; Series B
  The folders are arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  - Aakhus, Jerome E. and Kay (commander USS McGinty), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 44/1)
  - Aaltonen, Seppo, 1963 (Box-folder 44/2)
  - Aaron, Louise, 1962 (Box-folder 44/3)
  - Aladi, Dr. John, 1962 (Box-folder 44/4)
  - Abb, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/5)
  - Abdie, Jack, 1961 (Box-folder 44/6)
  - Abe--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 44/7)
  - Abhau, Capt. W. C., 196 (Box-folder 44/8)
  - Abplanalp, Marlene, 1963 (Box-folder 44/9)
  - Abr--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 44/10)
  - Abs, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 44/11)
  - Abts, Gerald, 1963 (Box-folder 44/12)
  - Ach--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 44/13)
  - Ack, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 44/14)
  - Acquistapace, Abe, 1961 (Box-folder 44/15)
  - Actipis, Dan, 1963 (Box-folder 44/16)
  - Adair--Adams, Irwin, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 44/17)
  - Adams, Jane--Adams, Nick, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 44/18)
  - Adams, Patty--Adamson, Michael, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 44/19)
  - Addison, Adele, 1964 (Box-folder 44/20)
  - Adelsheim, Martha A., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/21)
  - Adk--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/22)
  - Adl--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/23)
  - Adolph, Carol, 1962 (Box-folder 44/24)
  - Affolter, W.W., 1961 (Box-folder 44/25)
  - Aga--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 44/26)
  - Age--, 1962 (Box-folder 44/27)
  - Agl--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 44/28)
  - Agn--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/29)
  - Ahern, O.E., 1961 (Box-folder 44/30)
  - Ahlberg, Axel A., 1963 (Box-folder 44/31)
  - Ahm--, 1961 (Box-folder 44/32)
  - Ahnemiller, (Mrs.) Henry, 1961 (Box-folder 44/33)
  - Ahr--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44/34)
  - Aic--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 44/35)
  - Aik--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 44/36)
  - Ail--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 44/37)
  - Ainslie, Mrs. Sheldon, 1964 (Box-folder 44/38)
  - Aithen, James N., 1961 (Box-folder 44/39)
  - Aka--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 44/40)
  - Ake--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 44/41)
  - Aki--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 44/42)
  - Aklan, Batan, 1961 (Box-folder 44/43)
  - Akridge, Eddy, 1961 (Box-folder 44/44)
  - Akiwiwu, S.C., 1962 (Box-folder 44/45)
  - Ala, Leina, 1960 (Box-folder 44/46)
  - Alb--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/47)
  - Albert, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 44/48)
  - Albertson, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 44/49)
  - Ald--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 44/50)
  - Ale--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 44/512)
  - Alfidi, Joey, 1962 (Box-folder 44/52)
  - Ali--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 44/53)
  - Aljovin, (Mrs.) Gladys, 1964 (Box-folder 44/54)
  - Alkire, O. Sharon, 1961 (Box-folder 44/55)
  - Allan--Allemang, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 44/56)
  - Allen, A. Richard--Allen, Herrick Kidder (Mrs.), 196 (Box-folder 44/57)
  - Allen, Jean Leslie-Allen, L.R. (Mrs.), 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Allen, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/2)
  - Allison--Allyson, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/3)
  - Almond, Laren, 1963 (Box-folder 45/4)
  - Alo--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 45/5)
  - Alp--, 1964 (Box-folder 45/6)
  - Als--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/7)
  - Alt--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 45/8)
  - Alv--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 45/9)
  - Alysworth, L.W., 1962 (Box-folder 45/10)
  - Ama--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/11)
  - Amb--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 45/12)
  - Ame--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/13)
  - Ami--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 45/14)
  - Ammons, Sammie Earl, 1964 (Box-folder 45/15)
  - Amo--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45/16)
  - Amsler, Joseph Clyde, 1963 (Box-folder 45/17)
  - Amundson, John M., Jr., 1962 (Box-folder 45/18)
  - Amtmann, Fred, 1962 (Box-folder 45/19)
  - Anders, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45/20)
  - Andersen, charlotte--Anderson, Fred, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/21)
  - Anderson, Gerald---Anderson, Loyed, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/22)
  - Anderson, M. J.--Anderson, Susan, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/23)
  - Anderson, Tom--Andrick, Virginia, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/24)
  - Ang--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/25)
  - Anicker, John (Mrs.), 1964 (Box-folder 45/26)
  - Anka, Paul, 1964 (Box-folder 45/27)
  - Ann--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/28)
  - Ans--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 45/29)
  - Ant--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/30)
  - Apgar, Virginia, 1963 (Box-folder 45/31)
  - Apl--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 45/32)
  - App--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 45/33)
  - Ara--, 1963 (Box-folder 45/34)
  - Arbogast, Donna, 1962 (Box-folder 45/35)
  - Arc--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 45/36)
  - Ard--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45/37)
  - Are--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 45/38)
  - Arg--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 46/1)
  - Aries, Leonard A. (Dr.), 1963 (Box-folder 46/2)
  - Arling, Walter J., 1963 (Box-folder 46/3)
  - Arm--Armstrong, Herbert, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 46/4)
  - Armstrong, Jack--Armstrong, Neil A., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 46/5)
  - Arn--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 46/6)
  - Arq--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 46/7)
  - Arr--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 46/8)
  - Arthur, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 46/9)
  - Arasmith, Ed, 1964 (Box-folder 46/10)
  - Arvidson, Tom, 1963 (Box-folder 46/11)
  - Asa--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 46/12)
  - Asb--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 46/13)
  - Asc--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 46/14)
  - Ash--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 46/15)
  - Asp--, 1962 (Box-folder 46/16)
  - Ast--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 46/17)
  - Ata--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 46/18)
  - Atc--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 46/19)
  - Atiyeh, Victor G. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1962-1964 (Box-folder 46/20)
  - Atk--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 46/21)
  - Att--, 1961; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 46/22)
  - Atw--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 46/23)
  - Auborn, Gordon, 1963 (Box-folder 46/24)
  - Auchincloss, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 46/25)
  - Aud--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 46/26)
  - Auestad, Oscar Sr., undated (Box-folder 46/27)
  - Aug--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 46/28)
  - Aumont, Jean Pierre, 1961 (Box-folder 46/29)
  - Aune, Harold (Capt. and Mrs.), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 46/30)
  - Aus--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 46/31)
  - Aut--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 46/32)
  - Avalon, Frankie, 1963 (Box-folder 46/33)
  - Ave--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 46/34)
  - Avi--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 46/35)
  - Avshalomov, Jacob and David, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 46/36)
  - Axe, Toby, 1963 (Box-folder 46/37)
  - Axford, 1961 (Box-folder 46/38)
  - Axt--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 46/39)
  - Axum, Donna, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 46/40)
  - Aydelott, Guy (Rev.), 1963 (Box-folder 46/41)
  - Ayi--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 46/42)
  - Ayl--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 46/43)
  - Ayott, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 46/44)
  - Azu--, 1961-162; 1964 (Box-folder 46/45)
  - Bab--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 46/46)
  - Bac--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 46/47)
  - Bad--, 1962--1964 (Box-folder 46/48)
  - Bae--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 46/49)
  - Bafus, Theodore, 1962 (Box-folder 46/50)
  - Bag--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 47/1)
  - Bah--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 47/2)
  - Baier--Bailly, Frank, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Bain--Baird, 1959-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 47/4)
  - Baker, Alton--Baker, Joanna, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 47/5)
  - Baker, John--Bakken, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 47/6)
  - Balassan, Norik--Balin, Ina, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 47/7)
  - Ball, Carlton--Ballard, Joseph, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 47/8)
  - Ballin, Herb--Balsam, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 47/9)
  - Bam--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 47/10)
  - Ban--, 1961-1964; 1969 (Box-folder 47/11)
  - Baptist, Betsy, 1960 (Box-folder 47/12)
  - Baratta--Barksdale, Marie, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 47/13)